{
    "questions":[
        {
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Nikas",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Niggas", "Nokia", "Lakis"],
    "question":"Dogs name?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Rokas",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Klokas", "Tomas", "Lakis"],
    "question":"My name?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Mamyte",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Sigra", "Padaveja", "Mama"],
    "question":"Moms name?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Vegetables",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Fruits", "Sweets", "Italian"],
    "question":"Favorite food?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Creeping",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Jerking", "Fapping", "Sleeping"],
    "question":"Hobbies?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "2001",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["2000", "1999", "2002"],
    "question":"Year of birth?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "September",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["August", "June", "March"],
    "question":"Month of birth?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Homer Simpson",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Beetle Juice", "Goggins", "Zucc"],
    "question":"Favorite person?",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "19",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["20", "21", "22"],
    "question":"Age",
    "type":"string"
},
{
    "category": "personal",
    "correct_answer": "Water",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "incorrect_answers":["Lithuanika", "Coffee", "Tea"],
    "question":"Favorite drink",
    "type":"string"
}
]
}